A Guide to the Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music records FA1420
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 1957-1983; 2; 46.33 Cubic Feet 122 letter document boxes. Boxes 156-277.
  - E-F-G-H
    - Goldberg, Loretta (Box 196, Folder 15)
    - Goldberg, Louise (Box 196, Folder 16)
    - Golden Crest Records (Box 196, Folder 17)
    - Golden, Emily (Box 196, Folder 18)
    - Golden Fleece Limited (Box 196, Folder 19)
    - Golding, Maryann (Box 196, Folder 20)
    - Goldman, Lawrence (Box 196, Folder 21)
    - Goldovsky Opera Theater, 1964-1968 (Box 196, Folder 22)
    - Goldsmith, Diane (Box 196, Folder 23)
    - Goldstein, Loren (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Goldstein, Malcolm (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Goltry, Ms. Starleigh (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Gondek, Juliane (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Gonzaga, Otoniel (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Goodberg, Robert (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Goode, Daniel (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Goode, Richard (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Goodkin, Ira (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Goodsell, Jill (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Gordon, Eric A. (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - Gordon, Steven and Nadya (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - Goreniuc, Sue (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Gossett, Philip (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - Gottlieb, Gordon (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - Gottlieb, Jack (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - Gottlieb, Jay (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - Graff, Enrique (Box 197, Folder 18)
    - Graham, Elizabeth (Box 197, Folder 19)
    - Graham, Larry Michael (Box 197, Folder 20)
    - Graham, Ronald (Box 197, Folder 21)
    - Grahn, Ulf (Box 197, Folder 22)
    - Grant-Winn Duo (Cameron Grant and James Winn) (Box 197, Folder 23)
    - Grantham, Donald (Box 197, Folder 24)
    - Grants to Individuals (Chart), 1957-1967 (Box 197, Folder 25)
    - Graseck, James E. (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Gratton, Richard (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Grave, Floyd (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Graves, Mel (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Gray, Austin (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Gray, Bettina Bentrup (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Gray, Judith (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Gray, Robert (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - Grayson, David A. (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Great Falls Symphony Association (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Green, Nancy (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Greenawald, Sherri (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Greenbaum, Adrianne (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - Greenbaum, Matthew (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Greene, Gordon (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - Greene, James (Box 198, Folder 16)
    - Greene, Margo (Box 198, Folder 17)
    - Greer, Gordon (Box 198, Folder 18)
    - Grenadilla records (Box 198, Folder 19)
    - Gressel, Joel (Box 198, Folder 20)
    - Grettie, Carmela Bell (Box 198, Folder 21)
    - Griebling, Lynn (Box 198, Folder 22)
    - Griesheimer, James (Box 198, Folder 23)
    - Griffel, L. Michael (Box 198, Folder 24)
    - Griffin, Patricia (Box 198, Folder 25)
    - Griffin, Ralph (Box 198, Folder 26)
    - Grodecka, Deborah (Box 198, Folder 27)
    - Grof, Victoria (Box 198, Folder 28)
    - Groger, Julie (Box 198, Folder 29)
    - Gross, Hannah (Box 198, Folder 30)
    - Grossman, Helen S. (Estate of) (Box 198, Folder 31)
    - Grossman, Herbert (Box 198, Folder 32)
    - Grossman, Jerry (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Grossman, Orin (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Groton, Don (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Group for Contemporary Music, Inc. (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Guariglia, Rose Marie (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Guastaferro, Domenic (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Gubrud, Irene (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Guild for Contemporary Music, Inc. (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Guilmant Organ School (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Gurwitt, Dennis (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Guth, Otto (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Guthrie, Patricia (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Gutknecht, Carol (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - Guy, Larry (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Guyer-Hiller, Joyce (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Gwozdz, Lawrence (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - Ha, Mr. Jae Eun (Box 199, Folder 17)
    - Haas, Jonathan (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - Haddon, Judith (Box 199, Folder 19)
    - Hagan, Robert (Box 199, Folder 20)
    - Hagberg, Karen (Box 199, Folder 21)
    - Hagopian, Robert (Box 199, Folder 22)
    - Hahn, Marian (Box 199, Folder 23)
    - Haig, Susan Elizabeth (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Hailey, Christopher (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Hakim, Talib Rasul (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Haldaman, Constance (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Haleakala, Inc. (The Kitchen), 1978-1982 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Haleakala, Inc. (The Kitchen), 1975-1977 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Haley, Elizabeth (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Halfvarson, Eric (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Hall, Bruce (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Hall, Felipe (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Hall, Jeffrey (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Hall, Kenneth (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Hall, Kent (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Hall, Saundra (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - Hall, Thomas (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Hall, Vicki (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - Halpin, Brooke (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - Halprin, Diana (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - Halvorsen, Thomas (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Hamamoto, Clare (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Hamilton, Bonnie (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Hamilton, Gail (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Hamilton, Suzanne (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Hamilton, Thomas (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Hammel, William (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Hanani, Mr. Yehuda (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Hand, Frederic (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Handell, Darrell (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Handel and Haydn Society (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Han-Gorsky, Adam (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - Hanks, Sarah (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - Hanlon, Kevin F. (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - Hannay, Roger (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Hansen, Theodore C. (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - Haran, Michael (Box 201, Folder 17)
    - Harbison, John (Box 201, Folder 18)
    - Harden, Jean (Box 201, Folder 19)
    - Hardi, Katalin (Box 201, Folder 20)
    - Harford Theatre Association, Inc. (Box 201, Folder 21)
    - Harger, Gary (Box 201, Folder 22)
    - Harman, David (Box 201, Folder 23)
    - Harnes, Sondra (Box 201, Folder 24)
    - Harness, William (Box 201, Folder 25)
    - Harrington, Leslie (Box 201, Folder 26)
    - Harris, Donald (Box 201, Folder 27)
    - Harris, Kenneth (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Harris, Margaret (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Hart, Mary Ann (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Hart, Philip (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Hartway, James John (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Harvestworks, Inc. (Public Access Synthesizer Studio) (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Haskin, Howard (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Hassman, Ellen Zoe (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Hastings, Emily (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Hastings, Mary Logan (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Hatch, Peter (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - Hawley, William (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - Hawkshaw, Paul (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - Hayami, Ms. Kazuko (Box 202, Folder 14)
    - Hays, Doris (Box 202, Folder 15)
    - Hays, Elizabeth (Box 202, Folder 16)
    - Healy, Linda (Box 202, Folder 17)
    - Heath, Dennis (Box 202, Folder 18)
    - Heckman, Ronald (Box 202, Folder 19)
    - Heenan, Nora Jean (Box 202, Folder 20)
    - Hefling, Stephen (Box 202, Folder 21)
    - Hegierski, Kathleen (Box 202, Folder 22)
    - Heifetz, Robin Julian (Box 202, Folder 23)
    - Heiss, John (Box 202, Folder 24)
    - Held, Barbara (Box 202, Folder 25)
    - Heller, Duane (Box 202, Folder 26)
    - Hellermann, William (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Hemmen, Margaret (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Hendel, Liora (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Henigman, Mali (Ms.) (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Henry, Gurcell (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Henschel, Jane (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Herbert, Heidi (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Herman, Martin (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Heussenstamm, George (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - The William and Flora Hewlett Foundation (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Hibbard, William (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Hicks, David (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - Hicks, Kenneth (Box 203, Folder 13)
    - Hidden Valley Music Seminars (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - Higgins, Paula M. (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - High, Ronald (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - Hight, Walter (Box 203, Folder 17)
    - Hill, Jackson (Box 203, Folder 18)
    - Hill, Thomas (Box 203, Folder 19)
    - Hilson, Gail (Box 203, Folder 20)
    - Hinds, Ruby (Box 203, Folder 21)
    - Hios, Paulette (Box 203, Folder 22)
    - Hirschland, Evelyn (Box 203, Folder 23)
    - Hoback, James (Box 203, Folder 24)
    - Hobson, Bruce (Box 203, Folder 25)
    - Hobson, Ian (Box 203, Folder 26)
    - Hoch, Beverly (Box 203, Folder 27)
    - Hoches, Barbara (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Hodkinson, Sydney P. (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Hoffman, Miles (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Holdeman, Charles (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Holl, Herbert (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Holland, Mark (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Hollegue, Elizabeth (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Hollister, David M. (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Holloway, David (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Holzman, David (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Honolulu Symphony Society, 1966-1976 (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Hooker, William J. (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Hoover, Katherine (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Hopkins, Yvonne (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - Horizon Concerts, Inc. (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - Horn, Victoria K. (Box 204, Folder 16)
    - Hornschuch, John (Box 204, Folder 17)
    - Horowitz, Rise (Box 204, Folder 18)
    - Horvit, Michael (Box 204, Folder 19)
    - Horwood, Michael (Box 204, Folder 20)
    - Hoselitz, Ann (Box 204, Folder 21)
    - Hosley, Kenneth (Box 204, Folder 22)
    - Hosten, Kevin (Box 204, Folder 23)
    - Houpt-Nolen, Paulette (Box 204, Folder 24)
    - Houston Ballet (Box 204, Folder 25)
    - Houston Grand Opera Association, Inc. (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Houtchens, H. Alan (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Hovey, Serge E. (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Howard, Earl (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Howard, Joseph A. (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Howe, Hubert S., Jr. (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Howe, Martha Jane (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Howell, Standley (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - Howrani, Mr. Walid Raja (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Hoy, B. Hendricks (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Hudson, Joe (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Hudson, Ron (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Hudyma, Paula (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Hughes, Judith (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - Hughes, Robert (Box 205, Folder 15)
    - Humphrey, David (Box 205, Folder 16)
    - Hunt, Karen (Box 205, Folder 17)
    - Hunter, Marsha (Box 205, Folder 18)
    - Hunter, Phyllis (Box 205, Folder 19)
    - Hutcheson, Mr. Jere T. (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Hutchison, Warner (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Hyla, Mr. Lee (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - I-J-K-L
    - The Imagination Machine (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Immerso, John (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Incorporation - Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund, 1962-1970 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Independent Composers Association (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - India Navigation Recording Company (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Indianapolis - International Violin Competition (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Indianapolis Opera Company (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - Ingham, Michael (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - Institute for Studies in American Music (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - Institute of International Education (IIE) - Young Artists Project, 1960-1969 (Box 206, Folder 13)
    - Institute for Art and Urban Resources, Inc. (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Institute of International Education (IIE) - Music Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Institute of International Education (IIE), 1969-1981 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Insurance, 1973-1975 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Interaction (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Inter-Media Arts Center, Inc. (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - International Association of Music Libraries (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - International Bach Society, Inc. (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - International Chamber Music Festival (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - International Contemporary Music Exchange, Inc. (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - International Music Council (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - International Musicology Society (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - International Opera Center (Geneva), 1966-1969 (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - International Opera Center (Zurich), 1969-1980 (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Interval (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - IRCAM (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - ISCM (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - Isbell, Timothy (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - Isbin, Sharon (Box 208, Folder 14)
    - Isen, Richard (Box 208, Folder 15)
    - Isley, Christine (Box 208, Folder 16)
    - Ivanoff, Alexandra (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Ives (Charles) Centennial Festival - Conference (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Ives (Charles) Center for American Music (Roxbury, CT) (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Izenson, Roberta (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Jackson, Brenda (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Jacobs, Paul (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Jacobson, Robert (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Jaffe, Stephen (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - James, Carolyne (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - James, David and Robelyn Schrade (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - James, Judith (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - James, Thomas (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - Janes, Julianna (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - Jankowski, Loretta (Box 209, Folder 14)
    - Jannery, Arthur (Box 209, Folder 15)
    - Jaqua, Christina (Box 209, Folder 16)
    - Jaron, Shirley (Box 209, Folder 17)
    - Jarrett, Sandra (Box 209, Folder 18)
    - Jaworski, Warren (Box 209, Folder 19)
    - Jeffrey, Peter (Box 209, Folder 20)
    - Jenkins, Newell (Box 209, Folder 21)
    - Jenkintown Music School (Box 209, Folder 22)
    - Jennings, David (Box 209, Folder 23)
    - Jennings, John (Box 209, Folder 24)
    - Jensen, Claudia Rae (Box 209, Folder 25)
    - Jensen, James A. (Box 209, Folder 26)
    - Jensen, Milton (Box 209, Folder 27)
    - Jensen-Woodbury Duo (Box 209, Folder 28)
    - Jenson, Dylana (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Jergenson, Mr. Dale (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Jerome Foundation, Inc. (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Jeter, James (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Jetton, Sandra (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Jhunever, Rosalyn (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Johannson, Johanna-Karen (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, A. Paul (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Johnson, David (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, Douglas (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - Johnson, Eugene (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, James (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - Johnson, Janet Lynn (Box 210, Folder 13)
    - Johnson, Jean (Box 210, Folder 14)
    - Johnson, Joyce Lynne (Box 210, Folder 15)
    - Johnson, Karen (Box 210, Folder 16)
    - Johnson, Mary Jane (Box 210, Folder 17)
    - Johnson, Nancy (Box 210, Folder 18)
    - Johnson, Robert L. (tenor) (Box 210, Folder 19)
    - Johnson, Sidney (Box 210, Folder 20)
    - Johnson, Tom (Box 210, Folder 21)
    - Johnston, Ben - Partch Editing Project (Box 210, Folder 22)
    - Johnston, Bliss (Ms.) (Box 210, Folder 23)
    - Jolley, David (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Jonason, Lucille (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Jonason, Louisa (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Jones, Dwain (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Jones, Elga (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Jones, Gwendolyn (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Jones, Isola (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Jones, James (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Jones, Jennifer (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Jones, Joella (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - Jones, Mary Agnes (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Jones, Marzetta (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - Jones, Robert W. (Box 211, Folder 13)
    - Jones, Ruby (Box 211, Folder 14)
    - Jones, Samuel (The Lert Legacy) (Box 211, Folder 15)
    - Jones, Warren (Box 211, Folder 16)
    - Jones, Wendal (Box 211, Folder 17)
    - Jordan, Betty (Box 211, Folder 18)
    - Jordan, Diane (Box 211, Folder 19)
    - Jubal Trio (Box 211, Folder 20)
    - Juett, Richard (Box 211, Folder 21)
    - Julliard School of Music (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Jutt, Stephanie (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Kabala, Christopher (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Kagan, Susan (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Kail, Robert (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Kalins, Diana (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Kallberg, Jeffrey (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Kamp, Jane (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Kamsler, Bruce (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Kanach, Sharon (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Kane, John (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - Kang, Wha Ja (Ms.) (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - Kansas City Lyric Theatre - Correspondence, Brochures, Financial Statements (Box 212, Folder 13)
    - Kantor, Myron (Box 212, Folder 14)
    - Kapec, David (Box 212, Folder 15)
    - Kapell Trio (Box 212, Folder 16)
    - Kaplan, Vicki (Box 212, Folder 17)
    - Karasik, Gita (Box 212, Folder 18)
    - Karlins, M. William (Box 212, Folder 19)
    - Karlsson, Lise (Box 212, Folder 20)
    - Karnstadt, Cynthia (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Karousatos, Nicholas (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Karp, Barbara (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Kartman, Anita (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Kashkashian, Kim (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Kaspriskie, Elliott (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Katz, Helen-Ursula (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Kaufman, Arthur (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - Kaufman, Jeffrey (Box 213, Folder 9)
    - Kavanaugh, Patrick (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - Keats, Donald (Box 213, Folder 11)
    - Kebede, Ashenafi (Box 213, Folder 12)
    - Kechley, David (Box 213, Folder 13)
    - Keck, George R. (Box 213, Folder 14)
    - Keefe, Robert (Box 213, Folder 15)
    - Keeling, Geraldine (Box 213, Folder 16)
    - Kehrig, Diane (Box 213, Folder 17)
    - Keith, David (Box 213, Folder 18)
    - Keller, Paula (Box 213, Folder 19)
    - Keller, Peggy Sears (Box 213, Folder 20)
    - Keller, Rip (Box 213, Folder 21)
    - Kellock, Judith (Box 213, Folder 22)
    - Kelm, Linda (Box 213, Folder 23)
    - Kelsey, Philip A. (Box 213, Folder 24)
    - Kennedy (John F.) Center for the Performing Arts, 1970-1981 (Box 213, Folder 25)
    - Kennedy Center Productions, Inc. (Box 213, Folder 26)
    - Kennedy, Frederick (Box 213, Folder 27)
    - Kennedy, Katherine (Box 213, Folder 28)
    - Kennedy, Tim (Box 213, Folder 29)
    - Kennedy, Laurel (Box 213, Folder 30)
    - Kernfeld, Barry (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Kerrigan, Ellen (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Kessner, Daniel (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Ketchum, Janet (duo with Peter Segal) (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Kibler, Keith (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Kiddie, Douglas (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Kielar, David (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Kielbasa, Marilyn (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Kievman, Carson (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Kim, Daisietta (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - Kim, Hyung Bae (Mr.) (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - Kim, Jung-Ja (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - Kim, Ms. Soye (Box 214, Folder 13)
    - Kim-Stierlin, Ms. HyoungHyee (Box 214, Folder 14)
    - King, John (Box 214, Folder 15)
    - King, Roy (Box 214, Folder 16)
    - King, Sheryl (Box 214, Folder 17)
    - King, William (Box 214, Folder 18)
    - Kingman, Daniel (Box 214, Folder 19)
    - Kirk, Bonnie (Box 214, Folder 20)
    - Kirkbride, Jerry (Box 214, Folder 21)
    - Kirshbaum, Ralph (Box 214, Folder 22)
    - Kitzmuller, Karen (Box 214, Folder 23)
    - Klebl, Hedi (Box 214, Folder 24)
    - Klein, Lothar (Box 214, Folder 25)
    - Klepinger, Evelyn Hertzmann (Box 214, Folder 26)
    - Klinghoffer, Rona (Box 214, Folder 27)
    - Klose, Robert (Box 214, Folder 28)
    - Kloss, Sherry (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Klucevsek, Guy (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Knaack, Donald (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Knight, Kathleen (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Knopf, Paul (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Knowles, John (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Koblitz, David (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Kodaly Musical Training Institute (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - Kohn, Eugene (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - Kolb, Barbara (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - Kopp, James B. (Box 215, Folder 11)
    - Korczak, Paul (Box 215, Folder 12)
    - Koregelos, Angela (Box 215, Folder 13)
    - Korf, Anthony (Box 215, Folder 14)
    - Korn, Mitchell (Box 215, Folder 15)
    - Koschmann, Constance (Box 215, Folder 16)
    - Kosins, Martin (Box 215, Folder 17)
    - Kosse, Roberta (Box 215, Folder 18)
    - Kosteck, Gregory (Box 215, Folder 19)
    - Kotik, Petr (Box 215, Folder 20)
    - Kovach, Brian (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - Kowalke, Mr. Kim (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - Kowalski, Henryk (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - Kramer, Bruce (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - Kramer, Jonathan (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - Kramer, Richard A. (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - Krasovsky, Emanuel (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - Kreger, James (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - Kreider, Robert (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - Kreiger, Arthur (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - Krenek, Ernst Festival (Box 216, Folder 11)
    - Kresky, Jeffrey (Box 216, Folder 12)
    - Krichaf, Jack (Box 216, Folder 13)
    - Kriesberg, Matthias (Box 216, Folder 14)
    - Kroll, Mark (Box 216, Folder 15)
    - Krome, Jason (Box 216, Folder 16)
    - Kronos Quartet, 1977-1979 (Box 216, Folder 17)
    - Krupnick, Robert (Box 216, Folder 18)
    - Kruse, Steven (Box 216, Folder 19)
    - KSOR Radio (Oregon) (Box 216, Folder 20)
    - Kucharz, Lawrence (Box 216, Folder 21)
    - Kuhlmann, Kathleen (Box 216, Folder 22)
    - Kuick, Deborah (Box 216, Folder 23)
    - Kupferman, Meyer (Box 216, Folder 24)
    - Kurtzman, Jeffrey (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Kuzma, Sue Ellen (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - La Barbara, Joan (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - La Brecque, Rebecca (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - Lachert, Hanna (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - Laderman, Ezra (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - Ladewig, James (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - Laduvane (Box 217, Folder 8)
    - Laferrierre, Marie (Box 217, Folder 9)
    - Lake Erie Opera Theatre, 1969-1973 (Box 217, Folder 10)
    - Lake George Opera Festival - General Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 217, Folder 11)
    - Lake George Opera Festival, 1976-1982 (Box 217, Folder 12)
    - Lake George Opera Festival - General Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 217, Folder 13)
    - Lake George Opera Festival - Brochure, Flyers, Financial Reports (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - La MaMa E.T.C. (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - Lamb, John D. (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - Lamb, Marvin (Box 218, Folder 4)
    - Lambro, Phillip (Box 218, Folder 5)
    - Lamneck, Esther (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - La Monaco, Nel (Box 218, Folder 7)
    - Lamott, Bruce (Box 218, Folder 8)
    - Lamy, Catherine (Box 218, Folder 9)
    - Lancaster, Francis (Box 218, Folder 10)
    - Landfield, Bonnie (Box 218, Folder 11)
    - Landsman, Renay (Box 218, Folder 12)
    - Lane, Richard (Box 218, Folder 13)
    - Lang, Ellen P. (Box 218, Folder 14)
    - Langham, Jennifer (Box 218, Folder 15)
    - Langton, Sunny Joy (Box 218, Folder 16)
    - Lanka, Sylvia (Box 218, Folder 17)
    - Lansing, Liana (Box 218, Folder 18)
    - Lansky, Paul (Box 218, Folder 19)
    - L'Arema Chamber Ensemble (Box 218, Folder 20)
    - Large, Norman (Box 218, Folder 21)
    - Larson, Janice (Box 218, Folder 22)
    - LaRue, Jan (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - Lashley, Erma (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - Lathem, Thais (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - Lattimore, Martha (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - Laufman, Ms. Laurien (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - LaVake, Margaret (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - LaVoix, Jeanette (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - Lawergren, Mr. Bo (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - Lawler, Timothy (Box 219, Folder 9)
    - Lawrence, James Theodore (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - Lawrence, Jeffrey (Box 219, Folder 11)
    - Lawton, Frances (Box 219, Folder 12)
    - Lay, Laura (Box 219, Folder 13)
    - League of Women Composers, 1979 (Box 219, Folder 14)
    - Le Baron, Anne (Box 219, Folder 15)
    - Lebherz, Louis (Box 219, Folder 16)
    - LeClair Piano Quartet (Box 219, Folder 17)
    - Leclerc, Gerard (Box 219, Folder 18)
    - Lee, Mr. Dai Uk (Box 219, Folder 19)
    - Lee, Eugene (Box 219, Folder 20)
    - Lee, Ray Caroline (Box 219, Folder 21)
    - Lee, Thomas Oboe (Box 219, Folder 22)
    - Lefferts, Peter (Box 219, Folder 23)
    - Kentucky Opera Association, Inc., 1976-1978 (Box 219, Folder 24)
    - Legro, Dianne (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - Le Guin, Elisabeth Covel (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - Lehrman, Leonard (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - Leipsic, Martha (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - Leisner, David (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - Lennon, John Anthony (Box 220, Folder 6)